

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I have expanded my knowledge with 2 years of experience in FEND, UI and UX. I would love to keep learning more technologies and become a master in FEND while being able to start learning BEND on the way, therefore becoming a FullStack Developer in the hopefully near future. My long term goal is to have been able to develop web but also native applications. I would describe myself as flexible in roles and team oriented.

SKILLS

- Technologies:
- Javascript
- Typescript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node.js
- Jest
- Git Github
- MongoDB

Soft Skills:

- Team Work
- Creativity

React

Next.js

• Redux

AWS

Bootstrap

Bootstrap

ExpressJS

React Native

Material UI

- Critical Thinking
 Teaching/ Mentoring

LANGUAGES

Greek Fluent Albanian B2 English C1 German B1

CONTACT



+49 1577 1514616



b.brisilda1552@hotmail.com



https://brisildabushi.com/



Marienfelde. 12277, Berlin

SOCIAL







BRISILDA BUSHI

FEND WEB DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

APP SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

SKF Lubrication Managment Germany | Berlin | 01.2022 - Present

- Frontend Development: Worked on one project from beginning till now, our tech stack is utilising: AWS, Next.js, Typescript, Storybook, Jest combined with react testing library, SWR (Data fetching), internal component library combined with ant design and a lot of other micro components when needed.
- UI Design: I was the only UI Designer within the team. I was the one responsible for the initial draft of our current project and the one who maintained Figma files and adjusted components as needed within the design tool.
- UX Design: Worked a lot with UX together with a senior UX, in which I created a lot of Figma prototypes and was taking notes during usability tests.
- Concept ideation: As designer I would many times bring forth different ideas to management and receive feedback on how to proceed. I am a trully team oriented person and I like to help and be helped when needed.

DCI WEB DEVELOPER TUTOR

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH | Berlin | 01.2021 - 10.2021

- Live Coding and explaining exercises to my fellow students upon requests
- Explaining terms and usage regarding challenging concepts

EDUCATION

UX/UI DESIGN INTERMEDIATE

ReDI School of Digital Integration | Berlin | 08.2022 - 12.2022

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH | Berlin | 11.2020 - 12.2021

- Attending the one year full time course which includes technologies from MERN stack
- Finished and still working on all small and large projects assigned to me/my team successfully

CERTIFIED TRAINING PROFESSIONAL (1 WEEK)

Peter Knapp GmbH Coaches & Catalysts | Berlin | 09.2019 - 09.2019

CERTIFIED TRAINING PROFESSIONAL (1 WEEK)

Arvato Bertelsmann CRM Solution Germany | Berlin | 10.2018 - 10.2018

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN CIVIL ENGINEERING (BSCE) Technological Institute of Crete | Iraklion | 10.2010 - 02.2016

• Learned physics, statics and math to be able to calculate the weight power a house needs/uses to make it stable and functional